- We should call the police.
- Uh...
(Bernadette:)I left my phone downstairs.
(Howard:)Damn, so did I.
Wait, I have my iPad!
What are we gonna do,
(Howard:)e-mail 911?
That's not helpful!
(Howard:)You know I rely
on humor in times of stress.
(Bernadette:)Let me know when you start,
because that wasn't funny!
(Howard:)Is that the hot tub?
(Bernadette:)Who would use
our hot tub?
(Howard:)Well, the answer is both
more and less disturbing
(Howard:)than you think.
(Bernadette:)Who is it?
(Howard:)Stuart.
(Howard:)He heard me talking
about us going away.
(Howard:)I guess he decided
to invite himself over?
(Bernadette:)Should we say something to him?
(Howard:)Maybe. How 'bout,
"Hey, you look like
a boiled chicken breast"?
I meant like, "What
are you doing here?"
(Howard:)Nah, that's not gonna
hurt his feelings.